It's quite cute.
だいぶ可愛いですね
May I ask your name?
お名前を聞いてもいいですか?
I'm Ren.
レンです
Mr. Len.
レンさん
You're an adult, right?
ちゃんと成人してますよね?
yes.
はい
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
nice to meet you.
初めまして
When I saw you on SNS, I didn't expect to see someone so petite.
SNS上でお見かけした時、こんなに小柄な方が来ると思ってな
It was.
かった んで
I was surprised.
びっくりしたんですけど
If you just look at his face, don't you think it looks really hard to poke?
顔だけ見ると凄く、突きにくい感じって言われません?
picture?
え?
Won't you tell me?
言われないか
Can't you just see the face?
顔だけで見られないか
Ren-san is also quite a dad cutlet, is he someone who does that on a regular basis?
レンさんも結構パパカツ、普段もやる人?
When you have free time?
暇な時?
When I have free time.
暇な時
Do you also come to hotels?
ホテルとかも来ることがあるんですか?
It looks like the sun is facing me.
日が向いてあるみたいな
that's right.
そうです
Now, Ren is not saying whether he is married or in a relationship.
今レンさんは、彼、結婚とかお付き合いしてるかってこと言
Are you there?
います?
Yeah.
うん
Alone?
一 人に?
Yeah.
うん
How about one person?
一人にはどうですか?
I have free time.
暇ですね
Do you have free time every day?
日々暇?
I have free time every day.
日々暇
Are you serious?
マジですか?
Do you feel like you spend a lot of time at home?
なんかこう、結構家にいること多いって感じ?
Well, basically.
そうですね、基本
on the bed.
ベッドの上
On the bed?
ベッドの上?
On the bed...
ベ ッ ド の 上 で...
It's kind of rumbling.
なんかゴロゴロ
Purr.
ゴロゴロ
Lie down.
寝そべって
Go-ro-ro-ro.
ゴ ロゴロ
Would you like to see something?
なんか、見たりとかしないですか?
Videos, anime, dramas.
動画、アニメ、ドラマ
I do add some drama though.
ドラマとかは付けてるけど
Does it feel like you're wearing it?
付けてるって感じ?
Yeah, I can't concentrate.
そう、集中力なくて
So, what about the things that are included in the book that you sometimes look at?
じゃあ、たまに見るって書に付いてるのを?
Ah, if you're interested in the sound, check it out.
ああ、音が気になったら見る
So, what are you currently addicted to watching?
じゃあ、今はまって見てるものとか、
Nothing in particular?
特にない?
Nothing in particular.
特にない
Do you never read manga?
漫画読んだりとか、絶対しないですか?
I don't read manga because I have to pay for it.
漫画は課金しちゃうから読まない
What does it mean to pay and start reading?
課金、読み始めるとってこと?
I don't watch it because I get curious and end up paying for it.
気になって課金しちゃうから、見ない
So, has something like that happened in the past?
じゃあ、過去、そういうことはあった?
there were.
あった
Was it no good?
ダメだった?
Manga.
漫画は
Use it elsewhere.
他 で使って
I can't stop.
止まらん
Cell phone bills are expensive.
携帯代はやばい
You're definitely going to be an idiot.
確かに馬鹿になるんだよね
Don't you ever have lonely nights when you're alone?
一人だと、寂しい夜とかないですか?
With friends.
友達と
Do you not really have any desire to have a boyfriend?
彼氏とか欲しい願望もあんまりないですか?
No, I want what I want.
いや、欲しいのは欲しい
I don't have many encounters.
あんまり出会いがない
What type do you like?
どういうタイプが好きなの?
Or rather, I like it.
好きというか
With an adult who knows me and says it's great.
知って、とってもいいよって言ってくれる大人と
Do you like older people a lot?
年上は結構好きですか?
How many?
何個か
About a few.
数個ぐらい
This is the type it looks like.
見た目でいうとこういうタイプ
Doesn't she have a kind face?
優しい感じの顔じゃないですか?
It seems a little cold.
感じにちょっと冷たそうな
Is it a bit like both?
そのちょっと両方みたいな?
Because it feels bad if you're always acting up.
ずっとデレレレだと気持ち悪いから
Basically it's a little dry, but
基本はちょっとドライでもあるけど、
At random times.
ふとした時とか
At night, after taking a bath, when you're feeling tired, etc.
夜、お風呂あがりとか、 しんどい時とか、
I like people who like me.
好きやみたいな感じの人がいい
Well then, here's one person with hair who sometimes shows he likes her.
じゃあこう、 時々好きを見せてくれる髪の人が1個
Ah, that's the type.
あ、そういうタイプね
I think when we break up, the person we love is really like a cat.
別 れると僕は思うんですけど、 好きな人は本当に猫の振りとこ
I'm being attacked by
に やられてます
It's quite a bit swayed.
結構ちょっと振り回されるぐらいが
It's totally okay to swing around and be thrown around.
振り回すし振り回されるっていうのも全然大丈夫
It's quite nice to be allowed to be tossed around.
振り回し振り回されてるのが許容されるのが結構いいから
Is there anyone with a face like this?
この 顔型みたいなのいないですか?
There isn't one.
いないっすね
Your face type, how kind you are, etc.
顔のタイプとか、優しいとか
Do you have any other fetishes besides that?
そういうの以外に、なんかフェチ的なものとかないですか?
It just makes me feel so weird.
なんか無性にグッとくる
The muscles of the neck.
首の筋とか
首の筋
Is this what you mean?
こう いうとことか
Collarbone, neck swish.
鎖骨、首のシュッと
So, is there something wrong with people who are fat and buried?
じゃあなんか、太って埋もれてる人とかダメ?
No.
ダメー
So it's probably easier to get a fairly slender type?
じゃあ結構細身のタイプが多分出やすい?
Yes, about straight.
そう、真っ直ぐらい
When I took it off, it was surprisingly straight.
脱いだら意外と真っ直ぐ
If you take it off.
脱いだら
Now I'm looking forward to taking it off.
じゃあ脱ぐまでのお楽しみです
oh yeah.
そうそう
Men are pretty muscular, aren't they?
結構筋だと筋とか、男の人って割と筋張ってるじゃないですか
Blood vessels.
血管とか
What about blood vessels?
血管とかどうですか?
Blood vessels are also good.
血管もいいです
I wonder what's going on in my heart.
心はなんだって感じなんですけど
good.
いい
A fetish is something you carry on your back.
フェチって背負うもんね
Don't you have any clothes?
服装とかはないですか?
Dress neatly and casually.
服装は、きれいに、カジュアル
Like setup.
セットアップとか
I feel like it doesn't have to have any weird personality.
変に個性が出てなくていい感じ
Something like GU.
GUとか
Well then, it's Tanaka's GU setup.
じゃあGUセットアップの田中系です
That's nice.
いいですね
I'm sorry to tell you my story, but I have a pajama fetish.
僕の話で恐縮なんですけど、 パジャマフェチとかあって、
Do you know how I feel?
気持ち分かります?
Yeah, somehow.
うん、なんとなく
I understand.
なん と分かる
The gap is fine, but that's the point.
ギャップもええなんですけど、要は
What I said earlier may be a bit full-fledged, but
さっき言ってたの、ちょっとフルフルかもしれないですけど、
A lot of girls are usually fashionable,
結構女の子って普段、オシャレしてる方が、
I'm wearing my pajamas at home, I'm letting my guard down.
家でパジャマ着てる、油断してる
Isn't there something like that?
そういうのないですか?
Well, there is already a little bit.
もう、まあ、ちょっとはある
Does Lens-san wear pajamas at home?
レンスさんは、家でパジャマとか着る?
wear.
着る
It looks kind of fluffy.
なんか、モコモコっぽい
Today, I brought some terrorist-type stuff.
今日、僕、テロテロ系の持ってきたんですけど、
You can change your clothes if you like.
よかったら着替えてもらうことができますよ
yes.
はい
However, I had a hard time imagining that Mr. Rence was so short.
ただ、レンスさんがここまで小柄だとちょっと想像しなくて、
Maybe it's big.
もしかしたら大きいかもしれない
Well, I can personally get it, so
それはそれで、個人的にはもらえるので、
Can I have you change your clothes for a while?
ちょっと着替えてもらっていいですか?
I'll bring it.
持ってきます
It's like this, a cat.
こういうやつなんですけど、 ネコ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
It just happens to be a cat.
たまたまネコだ
I don't wear things like this often.
こういうのあんまり着ない?
This kind of material.
こういう素材は
summer?
夏?
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうです
Sorry, I'm just a little worried about the size.
すみません、サイズだけちょっと心配なんですけど、
What kind of thing is it?
どんなもんです?
Is it quite large?
だいぶ大きいかな?
I'll hide.
隠れますね
Are you going to wear it?
グルグルでじゃあ着ますか
What about above?
上は?
By the way.
ちなみに
But, is that it?
でも、あれか
Even though it's big on the top, it seems like it's fine.
上は大きくてもなんか、 それはそれで良さそうですね
Well then, you can ask me to change clothes.
じゃあ、着替えてもらってもいい
Is it?
ですか?
Ah, one person at a time.
あ、 一人ごとです
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
This is what I'm wearing.
こんな、 着けてますよ、これ
yes.
はい
You're wearing something so sexy.
こんなエロいの着けてるんですね
Yeah.
うん
Is the cloth loose?
ウエスのゆるゆる?
Loosely.
ゆるゆる
Hey everyone,
皆さんちょっと、
Yes, it's not.
うん じゃないですよ
Aren't your breasts quite big?
だいぶ、なんか、 おっぱい大きくないですか?
Not,
じゃなくて、
There are amazing things like Taniva.
タ ニバとかすごい素があ
Sorry for interrupting.
って、 ちゃちゃ入れてすみません
What do you think?
どうですか?
For me today.
今日こっち的には
Smooth.
さらさら
ERROR
夏って感じ?
Yeah.
うん
That's good.
いいっすね
It matches the image quite well.
なんか、イメージとかなり合いますね
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good to the touch today?
今日 手触りとか良い感じですか?
ERROR
さ らさら
さらさら?
ERROR
結構、テロテロって感じですもんね
Yeah.
うん
Smooth, smooth.
さらさら、さらさらっすね
I'm walking.
歩いてる
ERROR
あ、いろいろか
There are many things.
いろいろっすね
Yeah, I'm walking.
うん、歩いてる
ERROR
いろいろっすね
Where is this?
ここは?
It's in the seams though.
縫い目に入っててますけど
This is a bit scary, cat.
ちょっとこれ、ひわいな、 猫さん
It's full of cats.
猫だらけっすね
cute.
かわいい
Is it even in cats?
猫の中にもいるっすか?
There aren't any.
いないよ
ERROR
猫の中いない?
not present.
いない
What about this?
こっちは?
not present.
いない
not present?
い ない?
The pajamas look amazing and loose.
パジャマがすごい、ゆるゆる見えますね
width.
幅
I want a color like this.
こんな色したいっすね
Yeah.
うん
It was amazing, I could hear it, but
なんか すごい、声出てましたけど、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Well, let's just lie there on our backs.
じゃあ、そこに仰向きになってやりましょうか
It's sticking out.
はみ出てるね
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever used something that does this?
これ、するようなやつって使ったことないの?
Yeah.
うん
I'll try it.
やってみるよ
Yeah.
うん
It feels good.
いい感じだね
The one who comes first may not be a problem anymore.
先に来るやつとか、こっちはもう問題ないかも
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Yeah.
うん
Min-chan, do you want to do either?
みんちゃん、下、どっちだってやる?
Yeah.
うん
It's kind of amazing.
なんかすごい
It hurts so bad.
めっちゃ痛い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Maybe.
もしかして
It felt good.
気持ちよくなってたな
Yeah.
うん
Oh, that's dangerous, go first.
あ、そこやばい、先っちょ
First, first, that's dangerous.
先っちょ、先っちょやばい、そこ
Ah, I'll do it.
あー、やりますよ
What city.
どこだって
Yeah
うん
Yeah yeah.
うん うん
Stick your butt out a little.
ちょっと お尻突きだしてね
I could see Manjul's dick.
マ ンジュルチンコ見えてたんだけど
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It felt good.
気持ちよくなってた
Look here.
こっち見て
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I'm so sorry.
めっちゃごめん
It came out like a mess.
めちゃくちゃ出ちゃった
It was dripping outside, so let's do it.
外に垂れてきてたから、やりましょう
It might not be a mess.
めちゃくちゃないかも
Yeah yeah.
うんうん